warning: The `fitz` API is deprecated and will be removed in future. Use `import pymupdf` instead.
=== Research_on_Collaborative_Management_Mechanism_of_.pdf ===
--- PAGE 1 ---
� The Author(s) 2024.
www.omniscient.sg
                        � The Author(s) 2024. Open Access This article is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License
                 (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/), which permits unrestricted use, sharing, adaptation, distribution and 
reproduction in any medium or format, for any purpose, even commercially, as long as you give appropriate credit to the original author(s) 
and the source, provide a link to the Creative Commons license, and indicate if changes were made. 
Global Economic Perspectives Vol 2 Issue 2 2024
	
Original Research Article
Open Access
Research on Collaborative Management Mechanism 
of Scientific and Technological Innovation and Green 
Development in The Era of Digital Economy
Chun-Hai Lin
*
Guangxi University of Foreign Languages, Nanning, Guangxi, 530000, China
*Correspondence to: Chun-Hai Lin, Guangxi University of Foreign Languages, Nanning, Guangxi, 530000, 
China, E-mail: 271638304@qq.com
Abstract: In the era of digital economy, about the internal relationship between scientific and technological 
innovation and green development, this study launched an in-depth discussion, and analyzed the rapid 
development of digital economy and as a new driving force to promote green development. This paper 
expounds the key role of scientific and technological innovation in promoting green development, and 
probes into the importance of innovation model in realizing environme
--- PAGE 2 ---
Vol 2 Issue 2 2024
7 of 36
the government, enterprises and social organizations, 
to jointly formulate policies, promote scientific 
and technological innovation and green technology 
application, promote industrial transformation and 
upgrading, and achieve a more sustainable development 
model
[1]. Under the collaborative management 
mechanism, all parties need to fully cooperate and form 
a synergy to achieve a virtuous cycle of scientific and 
technological innovation and green development.
1. Background Analysis of Digital Economy
1.1 Development Trend of Digital Economy
The development trend of digital economy is an 
important direction of the current global economic 
development. In the context of the rapid development 
of information technology, digital economy has 
undoubtedly become an important engine for the 
economic growth of various countries. According 
to statistics, the huge scale of the global digital 
economy has exceeded 20 trillion US dollars, and the 
contribution rate of the digital economy in promoting 
global economic growth continues to rise. China's 
economic development has attracted worldwide 
attention and demonstrated the vitality of emerging 
economies, and the digital economy is also an important 
driving force for its sustained economic growth. The 
development of digital economy is of great significance 
to the establishment of a collaborative management 
mechanism for scientific and technological innovation 
and green development.
The deve
